你自己的真实声音。当然，并不存在唯一一种美国人的声音，甚至对
Your own true voice. There is not, of course, just one American voice, even for
同一个人也不是。人们会把声音和自己联系起来，
one person. People associate their voices with themselves, but have many different
人一生中会有不同的声音。你小时候的声音和成年后的声音不同。
voices throughout their lives. You have a different voice as a child than as an
成年人时不同，商务场合和聚会场合也不同。英国天体物理学家 Stephen Hawking
adult, different in business than at a party, and so on. Stephen Hawking, the
英国天体物理学家，在身体瘫痪之前说的是英式口音，
British astrophysicist, had an English accent prior to the paralyzation of his
声带瘫痪之前，说的是英式口音。后来使用带美国口音的机器人声音后，
vocal cords. After using a robotic voice with an American accent, he came to
他开始把自己和那个声音联系起来。几年后，DCT-01 语音合成器
associate himself with that voice. Several years later, DCT-01 voice synthesizer was
这个型号停产后，他拒绝换成带英国口音的型号。
discontinued, he declined to switch to a model with a British accent. He identified
他认同那个美国声音，并把它和自己联系起来。他说自己不想改变。
with the American voice and associated it with himself. I would not want to change
即使有人给他一个英国口音的声音，他也不想换。
even if I were offered a British-sounding voice. I would feel I had become a
否则他会觉得自己变成了另一个人。
different person," he said.